http://www.ccbaviation.com/information/9-privacy-policy.html

Remember me
Forgot your password?
Forgot your username?
04
LIFE'S TOO SHORT TO CRY (Special Limited Edition)
Data & Privacy Policy - UPDATED
Due to changes in the GDPR Regulations on May 25th 2018, we have updated our Policy. (30th April 2018)
(The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) (EU) 2016/679 is a regulation in EU law on data protection and privacy for all individuals within the European Union. It addresses the export of personal data outside the EU.)
Commitment To Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide
this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices
you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make
this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every
point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
The Information We Collect:
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on this website.
On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive
materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:
Name
Address
Email address
Phone number
On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example,
if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you
will need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance, the types
of personal information collected are:
Name
Address
Phone Number
The Information We DON'T Collect:
Credit/Debit Card Information
The Way We Use Information:
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order
only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside
parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order
only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information
with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
We offer gift-cards by which you can personalize a product you order for
another person. Information you provide to us to create a gift-card is only
used for that purpose, and it is only disclosed to the person receiving
the gift.
We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses
are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.
You can register with our website if you would like to receive general and marketing emails as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit
on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the
registration form and give your consent by enabling the options available.
Existing customers who registered before the changes were implemented, are required to amend their preferences and details, within the Account Maintenance section.
Once registered you are within your rights to cancel and opt out at any time from receiving such information by either contacting us directly, amending your account profile & details or by terminating your account.
All of our global marketing & general update emails do not disclose any details of the recipients. Additionally, such emails state clearly the opportunity for a customer on our mailing list to request removal and to no longer receive such material. Removal from the mailing list will still allow any registered customer to continue freely using the website and to make future purchases.
We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website
and to share with advertisers.
We never use or share the personally identifiable information
provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without
also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such
unrelated uses.
The Use of Shipping Data & Information:
1/ From time to time a registered customer may require to add the personal details of another individual or a different address from that registered under their own account. This is often due to an alternative shipping address being preferred, such as a business premises instead of a private one or on the occasion when a purchased item is a gift for somebody not registered with CCB Aviation Ltd.
If any shipping details (name and address) supplied during the placing of an order are different to that of the registered account holder, the user must acknowledge that any details provided are done so with full permission and consent. This can easily be done by selecting the check-box option within the shipping section of the checkout stage of the shopping cart, or by amending the Shipping Data within the Account Maintenance section of the registered account holder.
2/ Occasionally we may require a third party such as an Artist, Publisher or other Trade Supplier to ship directly an item purchased on behalf of CCB Aviation Ltd. Each registered customer is required to give their consent that the name & address details selected on the order may be shared for this purpose. Consent can be given by enabling the check-box provided during registration, within the Account Maintenance section of registered account holders or within the shipping section of the checkout cart.
Our Commitment To Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the
correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect
online.
Our Commitment To Payment Security
We currently offer two main secure payment facility options for registered customers.
1/ WorldPay. WorldPay is a global leader in payments processing technology and solutions for merchant customers. They operate reliable and secure proprietary technology platforms that enable merchants to accept a vast array of payment types, across multiple channels and are fully compliant with major Banks anywhere in the world.
CCB Aviation Ltd are fully compliant with the PCI Regulations required by Law in how we use and handle payment credit or debit card details. Our Certificate of Compliancy is updated each year by WorldPay who provide the independant secure payment facility.
Important Note: The Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS) applies to companies of any size that accept credit card payments. It is required of companies that intend to accept card payment, store, process and transmit cardholder data. It is required that we host your data securely with a PCI compliant hosting provider. WorldPay are a PCI compliant hosting provider.
2/ PayPal. PayPal has fast become one of the preferred methods of online payments. They allow guaranteed secure payments over the Internet with your credit card or bank account by taking your information once and then using that information to make payments to other parties. As an independant provider, PayPal are fully responsible for the processing, security and handling of ALL details provided during a transaction and it is also the responsibility of individual customers to maintain their personal accounts and details used, which are held with PayPal.
How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect
online and maintain it by either amending your account profile if registered or by simply sending
us an email. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.
You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information
by sending us a request that credibly shows error.
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps
to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
How To Contact Us
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies,
please contact us.
Order Basket
Your Cart is currently empty.
Vol. 2 (Signed Edition)
£145.00
AIR COMBAT PAINTINGS
VOL. 1 (Signed Edition)
SPITFIRE SORTIE by Nicolas Trudgian (Original Pencil Drawing signed by Battle of Britain pilots)
£495.00
Me262 JG7 by Nicolas Trudgian (Original Pencil Drawing signed by Luftwaffe pilots)
£495.00
Fw190 RED 1 JG300 by Nicolas Trudgian (Original Pencil Drawing signed by Luftwaffe pilots)
£395.00
TANK-BUSTER by Nicolas Trudgian (Original Pencil Drawing signed by RAF pilots)
HEADING HOME - AMERICAN AIRLINES DC3 - Ltd editions and Original Canvas painting
£40.00
HEADING HOME - AMERICAN AIRLINES CONVAIR CV990 - Ltd editions and Original Canvas painting
£40.00
HEADING HOME - AMERICAN AIRLINES 707 - Ltd editions and Original Canvas painting
£40.00
HEADING HOME - TWA SUPER CONSTELLATION - Ltd editions and Original Canvas painting
£40.00
HEADING HOME - TRANS CANADA DC3 - Ltd editions and Original Canvas painting
£40.00
HEADING HOME - BOAC COMET - Ltd editions and Original Canvas painting
£40.00
HEADING HOME - BEA VANGUARD - Ltd editions and Original Canvas painting
£40.00
HEADING HOME - BOAC VC10 - Ltd editions and Original Canvas painting
HURRICANE SCRAMBLE - (Rare Edition)
Website by www.RocXa.com.
valid XHTML and CSS.
CCB Aviation Limited is registered in England and Wales, Company number 5868499 | VAT Reg No: 867 3962 70
Terms and ConditionsTrading PoliciesCopyright NoticeReturns PolicyGuarantee
